Farm, if need be.
The animals decided unanimously to create a military decoration, Animal
Hero First Class, which was conferred there and then on Snowball and Boxer.
It consisted of a brass medal, they were really some old horse brasses which had
been found in the harness room, to be worn on Sundays and holidays.
There was also Animal Hero Second Class, which was conferred posthumously on the dead sheep.
There was much discussion as to what the battle should be called.
In the end, it was named the Battle of the Cowshed, since that was where the
ambush had been sprung.
Mr. Jones's gun had been found lying in the mud, and it was known that there was
a supply of cartridges in the farmhouse.
It was decided to set the gun up at the foot of the flagstaff, like a piece of
artillery, and to fire it twice a year, once on October the 12th, the
anniversary of the Battle of the